

Ahmed Alaaeldin Mohamed

Executive Manager Freelancer Trainer



(+20) 100-063-1030 / 127-078-9602



ahmed4alaa@gmail.com



Pi El Safa str, from El Arish str, Haram, Al Jisah, Egypt



www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed-alaaeldinmohamed

EDUCATION

Hospital Management Diploma

South Valley University Registered 2021

PR & Tourism Media

Sohag University 2002 - 2006

Certified Trainer

License S.N: 25032021631 - 2012 Cambridge University Egyptian Ministry of Education Egyptian Ministry of Foreign Affairs

Dr. Tarek Al-Swaidan

Dr. Ibrahim Elfiky

Dr. Soliman Al-Ali

Dr. Mohamed Abu Farha

Edu Master

Becert Academy USA

EXPERTISE

TRAINING & DEVELOPMENT LIFE COACHING **ENTREPRENEURSHIP** HEALTHCARE MANAGEMENT HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGEMENT CUSTOMER SERVICE MANAGEMENT **QUALITY MANAGEMENT**

SKILLS

MS WORD, EXCEL & POWERPOINT PHOTOSHOP & DESIGNING AutoCAD SENIOR LEADERSHIP SKILLS **TEAM BUILDING & MANAGEMENT** PROBLEM SOLVING STRATEGIC THINKING & FORESIGHT **DECISION MAKING** EMPLOYEE DEVELOPMENT CHANGE MANAGEMENT SKILLS **EXCELLENT COMMUNICATION SKILLS PUBLIC SPEAKING**

PROFILE

I have a clear, logical mind with a practical approach to problemsolving and a drive to see things through to completion. I have overall 15 years of work experience. I have more than 7 years of experience in managing and leading teams across multiple sectors, as well training individuals and groups. I am eager to learn, I enjoy overcoming challenges, and I have a genuine interest in Business Management, Entrepreneurship and making organizations more successful to reach their goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ADMINISTRATION MANAGER - ELECTRIC Dep.

GAMA Construction / 2020 - Present

EXECUTIVE MANAGER

Pharaohs Medical Service / 2016 – 2020

Managing Director

Tiba Royal Hospital / 2014 – 2016

Int. (CS & Insurance Claims) Assistant Manager South Sinai Hospital / 2010 - 2014

Int. (CS & Insurance Claims) Officer

Nile Hospital / 2007 - 2009

Casher

METRO Market / 2006 - 2007

PROJECTS & MEMBERSHIPS

Projects:

- ✓ El Shifaa Hospital Establishment 2016
- ✓ El Rehab Medical Center 2020

Memberships:

- ✓ Egyptian Youth Ambassador Egyptian Youth Ambassadors Authority
- ✓ Vice President of the Education Committee, 2020 Leadership Institution for Management Science & Development, Egyptian
- **Training Committee Member, 2020** The International Union of Economic and Diplomatic Cooperation, UK
- ✓ Regional Trainer, 2020 Ministry of Culture, Qena Branch
- Certified Trainer, 2020 Alfanya Alalamia for Training, Libya,

LANGUAGES SPOKEN

Arabic English *** German * * * * *

TRAINING SPECIALTY

BUSINESS MANAGEMENT HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGMENT CUSTOMER SERVICE MANAGEMENT **CUSTOMER RELATION MANAGEMENT** LEADERSHIP STRATEGIC PLANNING HOSPITAL MANAGEMENT SOFT SKILLS FAMILY RELATIONSHIP CONSULTING **ENTREPRENEURSHIP** LIFE COACHING PROFESSIONAL NURSING SKILLS

HOBBIES











PERSONAL INFO

NATIONALITY: EGYPTIAN

D.O.B: 25/03/1986 **MILITARY: EXEMPTED**

MALITARY: MARRIED WITH CHILDS

DRIVING LICENSE: YES PASSPORT: YES

- ✓ Fire Brigade Team Member, 2013 Civil Protection Department, Ministry of Police,
- ✓ Life Coaching & Creative Thinking, 2012 **Gulf Innovation for Training**
- ✓ Training of Trainer (TOT), 2012 Canadian Training Center of Human Development
- ✓ Human Development Diploma, 2012 Canadian Training Center of Human Development Edu-Master Training & Development
- √ HD Diploma, 2012 (NLP (Level 1, 2) - Managing Priorities - Mind Maps - Law of Attraction - Self-Confidence -Speed Reading - Hypnosis - Recruitment & Team Building - Business Communication Skills - Stress Management & Crisis - Creative Thinking -Secrets of Your Abilities - Memory & Remembering) Edu-Master Training & Development

CONFERENCES & EVENTS

- ✓ "Entrepreneurship Skills" webinar Tawar W Ghayar, 2021
- ✓ "Digital Transformation" webinar Tawar W Ghayar, 2021
- ✓ "Startup Pitch Bootcamp" webinar Founder Institute Tunisia, 2021
- ✓ "Education & Learning Strategies" Webinar Nahdet Misr, 2021
- "Job Planning" Webinar EYouth, Ministry of Youth, 2021
- ✓ "SMART GOALS" Webinar EYouth, Ministry of Youth, 2021
- ✓ Trainer: Decision making for students Masnaa Al Sukkar Primary School, Dishna, 2020.
- **Speaker: Labor Market Challenges** Admin Student Activity, Cairo University, 2017
- **Trainer: Nursing Professional Skills** El Shifaa Hospital, 2017
- **General Manager & Main Speaker** "Qualifying Youth for Labor Market" 1st Youth Conference, Qena, 2017
- Main Speaker: Strategic Planning Maady Runner, Cairo, 2016
- **Trainer: AHD Diploma Fresh Graduate** Uni Courses for Training, Sohag, 2015

TRAINING & CERTIFICATES

- **Business & Entrepreneurship Skills, 2020** Ministry of Youth & Sports
- **Project Planning, 2019** Uni Courses for Training
- Social Medical Marketing, 2019 Uni Courses for Training
- ✓ Mini MBA, 2018 Uni Courses for Training ✓ Quality Management, 2017 Uni Courses for Training
- German Language Level:B2, 2016 Uni Courses for Training
 - Safety & Healthy Work Environment, 2011 National Center for Safety & Healthy Work Environment
 - ✓ Building Relationships, 2010 American Chamber of Commerce
 - ✓ Project Management Professional (PMP 2009), 2010 American Chamber of Commerce
 - ✓ Customer Service Business Ethics Effective **Business Communication, 2010** American Chamber of Commerce
 - ✓ Fundamentals of Business Management, 2010 American Chamber of Commerce
 - ✓ Training of Trainer (TOT), 2010 Edu Master for Training
 - ✓ Business English Grammar, 2010 American Chamber of Commerce
 - ✓ German Language, 2006 Mega Soft Training Center